export const Questions = [
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following is not a programming language?",
        optionA: "C++",
        optionB: "Python",
        optionC: "HTML",
        optionD: "All of them",
        answer: "Option C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "React is a framework of which?",
        optionA: "CSS",
        optionB: "JavaScript",
        optionC: "HTML",
        optionD: "BootStrap",
        answer: "Option B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following is not a frontend technology?",
        optionA: "PHP",
        optionB: "CSS",
        optionC: "ReactJs",
        optionD: "None of them",
        answer: "Option A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is full form of PHP?",
        optionA: "Pre Hypertext Processor",
        optionB: "Preprocessor Hypertext",
        optionC: "Preprocessed Hypertext",
        optionD: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
        answer: "Option D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following concurrency control protocols ensure both conflict serializability and freedom from deadlock?",
        optionA: "2-phase locking",
        optionB: "Time-stamp ordering",
        optionC: "None of them",
        optionD: "All of them",
        answer: "Option B",
    },
    {
        prompt: " What is GIT?",
        optionA: "Version Control System",
        optionB: "Website",
        optionC: "Keep Projects",
        optionD: "Contain Repository",
        answer: "Option A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following is a SQL type database system?",
        optionA: "MongoDB",
        optionB: "MultiMedia Database",
        optionC: "Relational Tables",
        optionD: "Cassandra Database",
        answer: "Option C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is API?",
        optionA: "Application Program Interface",
        optionB: "Application Programming Interface",
        optionC: "App Program Interface",
        optionD: "Application Programming Interaction",
        answer: "Option B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of following is/are styling process in CSS?",
        optionA: "Inline",
        optionB: "Internal",
        optionC: "External",
        optionD: "All of them",
        answer: "Option D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the purpose of HTML?",
        optionA: "Make Website Responsive",
        optionB: "Make website working",
        optionC: "Structuring the Website",
        optionD: "None of them",
        answer: "Option C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following activities do we perform while declaring useState in react?",
        optionA: "Object destructuring",
        optionB: "Unpacking object",
        optionC: "Array destructuring",
        optionD: "Unpacking array",
        answer: "Option C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which type of variable can we define in the useState hook?",
        optionA: "Integer",
        optionB: "String",
        optionC: "List",
        optionD: "All of the above",
        answer: "Option D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Can we use useState hook inside conditional statement such as: if or while?",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
        optionC: "Yes: In Some Case",
        optionD: "No: In Some Case",
        answer: "Option B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is full form of NPM?",
        optionA: "Node Processor Medium",
        optionB: "Node Procedure Module",
        optionC: "Node Processing Module",
        optionD: "Node Package Manager",
        answer: "Option D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which method of fs module is used to delete a file?",
        optionA: "fs.delete(fd, len, callback)",
        optionB: "fs.remove(fd, len, callback)",
        optionC: "fs.unlink(path, callback)",
        optionD: "None of the above.",
        answer: "Option C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What is the Context API in React used for?",
        optionA: "Creating Components",
        optionB: "Sharing data b/w Components",
        optionC: "Styling Components",
        optionD: "All of them",
        answer: "Option B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "What does the createContext function return?",
        optionA: "A Provider & Consumer Component",
        optionB: "A Higher-order component",
        optionC: "None of them",
        optionD: "A Render Prop",
        answer: "Option A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which SQL statement is used to extract data from a database?",
        optionA: "SELECT",
        optionB: "OPEN",
        optionC: "GET",
        optionD: "EXTRACT",
        answer: "Option A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which SQL statement is used to insert new data in a database?",
        optionA: "ADD NEW",
        optionB: "INSERT NEW",
        optionC: "ADD RECORD",
        optionD: "INSERT INTO",
        answer: "Option D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following concurrency control protocols ensure both conflict serializability and freedom from deadlock?",
        optionA: "SELECT Persons.FirstName",
        optionB: "EXTRACT FirstName FROM Persons",
        optionC: "SELECT FirstName FROM Persons",
        optionD: "None of them",
        answer: "Option C",
    }
];